Chevrolet Spark car you can get
with easy installments and
high approval rate through
rajamobil.com rajamobil.com network
is very wide to all car dealers
makes it easy for you to get
your dream car small capacity car
and small dimensions and
have a small passenger capacity
is one of the cars that
has many fans in Indonesia
this car which is usually called sitikar started to
appear in 2004 where the Honda Jazz
first appeared as a pioneer of city
car which has rumors Where the dot
on the letter j on the Honda Jazz comes
from a diamond stone which if
sold has a fairly high price
has a fairly small dimension
makes this car does not take up
too much space when used to be
one of the favorite cars of
college students who have just been bought a car
by their parents some sitikar that are selling
well in the Indonesian market
include the Honda Jazz Toyota
Yaris Nissan March Mitsubishi Mirage and
the latest is the Chevrolet Spark
which is a product of the
American manufacturer Chevrolet or often
abbreviated as CV this is
one of the United States manufacturers that
has several products including the
sparky which breathes the spirit
of sitikar which has the characteristics
of small dimensions small passenger capacity
and fuel consumption which is also
small this car uses a
1.4 engine capacity  l which can
produce power of 98 peta seconds
at 6200 revolutions per minute and
torque of 128 n m at 4400 revolutions
per minute is quite small compared
to other sitikar friends, the engine
and dimensions of this small car, the cevrolet Spark,
have an engine and dimensions that are
indeed very small for the size of a sitikar
in today's era, the engine capacity is 1200
cm3 with a diameter X stroke of 74 mm by
81.com 3 mm, this small engine
can certainly produce enough power to
accompany your journey through
traffic jams in the afternoon, the maximum power of
this car reaches 98 peta seconds at
6200 revolutions per minute and its
torque is 128 n m at 4400
revolutions per minute, engine type 1.4 l DOHC
AC 4-cylinder vvt diameter X stroke 74
mm by 81.com 3 mm maximum power 98
peta seconds 6200 revolutions per minute
maximum torque 128 n m 4400 revolutions per minute
transmission system continuously variable
transmission CVT cylinder capacity
1399 cm3  multi point fuel
injection system gasoline fuel
drive by wire steering system the dimensions of the Spark are
very small, even
closer to LCGC or Low Cost green car
than a city car that is now being compared,
even closer to the shape of a
check, eliminating the philosophy of a city car that is
deliberately small and
has a small engine, the length of
this car only reaches
3636 mm, then the width is
1595 mm and the height is
1476 mm, it is not suitable for
people with a height of more than 170 cm
and weighing 90 kg because
their heads will definitely hit the roof of the car which is not
too high, the length of the car is
3636 mm, the width of the car is
1595 mm, the height of the car is
1476 mm, the weight of the car is
1094, the wheel axle is
2385 mm, the front tread is 730 mm, the
rear tread is 520 mm, the tank capacity is
32 liters, the passenger capacity is five people, the
ground clearance is
159 mm, the chassis is tires and brakes Chevrolet Spark
Chevrolet Spark which is small and has a
very small body is of course
still equipped with a chassis and
legs that are quite capable of
pampering your laziness when you have to
face  The capital's super
duper crowded streets, this car has a
drive by wire steering system that makes it
light and remains under control. If you
want to accelerate the speed, then the suspension,
tires, and brakes that accompany the movement of
this car are also quite capable of
providing safety and comfort for
you. The front suspension uses a
Macpherson strut with coil springs
assisted by a rear suspension that
uses a compound crying with coil
springs guaranteed to make you
comfortable and forget a little that
this car has very small dimensions
for the size of the tires used in
this car have a size of
165/65 r14 and a disc braking system
at the front and a drum at the
rear. The steering system is electric power
steering drive by wire. The tire size is 165/65 r14. The
front suspension is Macpherson,
just tweet coil spring. The
rear suspension is cream compound with coil springs. The
front brakes are disc brakes. The rear brakes are drum.
The exterior of the Chevrolet Spark Chevrolet
Spark is a product from Chevrolet that
has the smallest dimensions. The
smallest engine. The smallest passenger capacity
and of course the cheapest price. The
Chevrolet Spark besides having a
price that is not much different from the
Agya and Ayla, the exterior is also quite
beautiful for the size of a car that has
American blood in its design curves from
the front of the car that just
got its live phase in the year.  2018
has a pretty pretty face and
attracts attention for prospective
consumers wide x-shaped grille
equipped with hanicom
in the middle complete with good
from CV which looks more sturdy than the
body of this car itself fog lamp
shaped box on the lower bumper
indirectly adds to the
functional side of this car the
main lamp is oval with a bulb
that uses a projector type halogen
looks ordinary quite pretty
because it is coated with a drl that
uses LED continues to the
side and rear Chevrolet Spark
has the characteristics of a cevrolet that is a
box-shaped car but the aerodynamic curve design
on Spark is more visible
especially at the back giving a
very thick modern impression and not
outdated compared to
other cars of the same type The
rear side of Spark is also no less
beautiful with the side of this car
rear combination lamp shaped
elongated downwards with
large lights is considered suitable to accompany the car trunk door
and bumper which also looks
quite good and modern of course the interior of the
Chevrolet Spark beautiful exterior
makes this car also has an interior
that is quite pleasing to the eye especially
for young people who crave
efficiency rather than functionality and
toughness interior meet or multi
information display this car looks
quite able to meet the expectations of
prospective consumers who are indeed  aiming for
this car steering wheel equipped with audio
control panel then
7 inch display unit with
smartphone integration technology that supports
Bluetooth connection In addition the interior of
this car also has a color that is quite
attractive to look at, namely jetblack
produces a bright black color
but is not striking the seats in the
second row can be folded with a 60
to 40 configuration which gives the effect of the
scope of the trunk to be wider and
able to accommodate more items
Chevrolet Spark safety features even though
this car has a very
small body and engine power that is not
too big but Chevrolet engineers
are very focused on safety
for drivers and passengers in
this car several main features such as
dual airbags then electronic stability
and Hill start assist really help
drivers to drive this car
to the destination point as a car
created with American blood
and has a market share of young people
makes the Chevrolet Spark have a bit of an
identity crisis where Chevrolet is known
for its
large and sturdy cars that if hit
with a wall then the wall is defeated
compared to this car